<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://amplifiedapparel.com/blogs/news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://amplifiedapparel.com/blogs/news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://amplifiedapparel.com/blogs/news/tagged/guitarist.atom"/>
  <title>Amplified Apparel - Amplified Apparel Blog</title>
  <updated>2018-03-17T12:44:00-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Amplified Apparel</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://amplifiedapparel.com/blogs/news/october-electric-guitar-t-shirt-design-howling-werewolf</id>
    <published>2017-10-01T00:00:05-04:00</published>
    <updated>2017-10-01T00:00:05-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://amplifiedapparel.com/blogs/news/october-electric-guitar-t-shirt-design-howling-werewolf"/>
    <title>October Electric Guitar T-Shirt Design: Howling Werewolf</title>
    <author>
      <name>Jeff Garris</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><span>Halloween is almost here! This month's t-shirt design gets a theme for the upcoming spooky season. I cooked up tons of ideas this year for new Halloween designs, but I only have so much time to create them, so I went with my favorite.</span></p>
<p><span mce-data-marked="1">I was browsing Halloween themed images online and this design immediately jumped into my head when I saw a werewolf. I knew how I wanted him to be standing and what I wanted the scenery to look like. I really enjoyed creating the artwork for this shirt and I hope that it will help get you into the Halloween spirit.</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://amplifiedapparel.com/blogs/news/steve-vai-who-i-think-is-the-greatest-guitarist-of-all-time</id>
    <published>2017-08-25T00:40:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2017-08-26T14:27:17-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://amplifiedapparel.com/blogs/news/steve-vai-who-i-think-is-the-greatest-guitarist-of-all-time"/>
    <title>Steve Vai on Allan Holdsworth</title>
    <author>
      <name>Jeff Garris</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><span>Steve Vai and I don't have a whole lot in common. He's a <em>way </em>better guitarist then me and he has a much cooler look then me. The one thing that we do have in common, though, is that we have a hard time calling anyone the greatest guitarist of all time.</span></p>
<p>Stevie Ray Vaughan is definitely my favorite, but I wouldn't be so bold as to call him the best of all time. While Steve Vai was listing out some of the greats in his interview with <a href="http://www.musicradar.com/news/steve-vai-these-are-the-guitarists-that-blew-my-mind" target="_blank" title="Steve Vai: these are the 10 guitarists that blew my mind" rel="noopener noreferrer">Music Radar</a>, he did propose that Allan Holdsworth could possibly hold that coveted title in his mind. Here's what he had to say:</p>
<p>"I very rarely agree with the term best guitar player. It just seems so obscene to put something so subjective into a best category.</p>
<p>"But if I had to say there was one, I would pick Allan Holdsworth.</p>
<p>"He was unique in ways that I don't think have been discovered yet. Many musicians can be considered ahead of their time, but usually - they're not. They're mainly ahead of everyone else at that time.</p>
<p>"For example, Jimi Hendrix wasn't ahead of his time; he was perfect for his time and ahead of everyone else.</p>
<p>"Allan Holdsworth was definitely ahead of his time because it's hard to realize how great he is - not many people actually understand. It takes time for us to catch up with those that are ahead of their time.</p>
<p>"I would not be surprised if in 100 years from now, if people are still even listening to guitar - which I suspect they will be - he'll be singled out as 'the one' alone, so to speak.</p>
<p>"The way he uses the whole tone scale is like his own baby shoes - it's so easy for him. His thought process was phenomenal.</p>
<p>"I can hear any guitar player and I know what they're doing - I might not be able to play it - but I can see it in my mind's eye.</p>
<p>"But I do not know what the fuck Holdsworth was doing at all..."</p>
<p>I honestly had never heard of Holdsworth, but you can bet that I looked him up immediately. I don't really even know how to describe what I found. It's this sort of jazz fusion madness and there's something in his playing that I can't explain; it's mesmerizing and a bit confusing. The guy is all over the fretboard, manipulating notes that I had no idea even belonged together. I don't know if he's the greatest guitarist of all time, but he's got to be up there.</p>
<p>Sadly, in my research I also found that he passed away not long ago on April 15, 2017. Have a listen and help keep <a href="https://youtu.be/TYiVWl9l804?t=2m" target="_blank" title="Allan Holdsworth Trio 2010-11-09 Leverkusen, GR" rel="noopener noreferrer">Allan Holdsworth's music</a> alive.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
