<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://amplifiedapparel.com/blogs/news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://amplifiedapparel.com/blogs/news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://amplifiedapparel.com/blogs/news/tagged/hard-rock.atom"/>
  <title>Amplified Apparel - Amplified Apparel Blog</title>
  <updated>2018-03-17T12:44:00-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Amplified Apparel</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://amplifiedapparel.com/blogs/news/new-womens-leggings-life-is-short-rock-it</id>
    <published>2018-03-17T12:44:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2018-03-17T12:47:58-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://amplifiedapparel.com/blogs/news/new-womens-leggings-life-is-short-rock-it"/>
    <title>New Women&apos;s Leggings! Life Is Short. Rock It.</title>
    <author>
      <name>Jeff Garris</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[These <a href="https://amplifiedapparel.com/collections/leggings/products/life-is-short-rock-it-leggings" target="_blank" title="Women's Rock Leggings" rel="noopener noreferrer">women's leggings</a> are rock inspired with a hint of motivation. Whatever it is that you do or want to be doing, whether it's working out, running a successful business, or jamming up on...<p><a class="read-more" href="https://amplifiedapparel.com/blogs/news/new-womens-leggings-life-is-short-rock-it">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>These <a href="https://amplifiedapparel.com/collections/leggings/products/life-is-short-rock-it-leggings" target="_blank" title="Women's Rock Leggings" rel="noopener noreferrer">women's leggings</a> are rock inspired with a hint of motivation. Whatever it is that you do or want to be doing, whether it's working out, running a successful business, or jamming up on stage to a crowd of screaming fans, you have to stop dreaming about it and start doing it. There's no time to waste. Life is short. Rock it.</p>
<p><span>Product Features</span></p>
<ul>
<li>82% polyester/18% spandex fabric blend</li>
<li>Four-way (horizontal and vertical) stretch</li>
<li>Comfortable and smooth microfiber yarn</li>
<li>Elastic waistband</li>
<li>White fabric lining (avoid embarrassing bend-over moments)</li>
<li>All-over printing offers unlimited and unrestricted design possibilities </li>
</ul>
<p>If there's anything that you'd like to see more of, electric guitar, acoustic guitar, metal, whatever, leave us a note and let us know. We love hearing from you.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://amplifiedapparel.com/blogs/news/october-electric-guitar-t-shirt-design-howling-werewolf</id>
    <published>2017-10-01T00:00:05-04:00</published>
    <updated>2017-10-01T00:00:05-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://amplifiedapparel.com/blogs/news/october-electric-guitar-t-shirt-design-howling-werewolf"/>
    <title>October Electric Guitar T-Shirt Design: Howling Werewolf</title>
    <author>
      <name>Jeff Garris</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><span>Halloween is almost here! This month's t-shirt design gets a theme for the upcoming spooky season. I cooked up tons of ideas this year for new Halloween designs, but I only have so much time to create them, so I went with my favorite.</span></p>
<p><span mce-data-marked="1">I was browsing Halloween themed images online and this design immediately jumped into my head when I saw a werewolf. I knew how I wanted him to be standing and what I wanted the scenery to look like. I really enjoyed creating the artwork for this shirt and I hope that it will help get you into the Halloween spirit.</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://amplifiedapparel.com/blogs/news/september-guitar-t-shirt-design-no-soft-rock</id>
    <published>2017-09-01T13:28:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2017-09-14T23:45:02-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://amplifiedapparel.com/blogs/news/september-guitar-t-shirt-design-no-soft-rock"/>
    <title>September Guitar T-Shirt Design: No Soft Rock</title>
    <author>
      <name>Jeff Garris</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>More guitar t-shirts are coming! This month is the start of something new for Amplified Apparel. I'm going to be kicking out a new design every month. Why? Because you need more guitar t-shirts and I'm going to make sure that you get them! I know, I know, I'm the best.</p>
<p>OK, so it's not all about you. I really enjoy coming up with new design ideas, fleshing them out, and then creating the final product for you to enjoy. In this case I was actually working on a different, yet related, design when I came up with this <a href="https://amplifiedapparel.com/products/no-soft-rock-t-shirt" title="No Soft Rock Guitar T-Shirt">guitar t-shirt</a>. It's funny how that happens sometimes. The point is that I create these shirts with joy and I hope that you'll wear them with the same passion.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
